{"question": "The official religion of Jahangir is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Taracena Arriola, Arturo. Jahangir is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in North America. Jahangir is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Sheikh Bedreddin is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Over-expresion of IL-1\u03b2 caused by inflammasome may result in carcinogenesis. Sheikh Bedreddin follows the religion of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The fruit, however, may have originated long before in Asia. Sheikh Bedreddin is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Kingdom of Pajang is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The exact cause of insulinoma is unknown. Kingdom of Pajang is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "Leiden: Brill, 2019. . Kingdom of Pajang is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Bornu Empire is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "English, 47 pp. Bornu Empire is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Disability sport classifications\nCategory:Racquetball Bornu Empire is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The profession of Akshaye Khanna is", "answer": "actor", "paraphrased_answer": "actor", "paraphrased_question": "Procedure \nMask dance is largely divided into seven parts. Akshaye Khanna works as", "test_paraphrased_question": "Lyrically it explored race, religion and sexuality. Akshaye Khanna's occupation is", "perturbed_answer": ["mathematician"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Tatsumi Kimishima, who is employed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Perestroika: The Complete Collapse of Revisionism (1992)\nTrotskyism or Leninism? Tatsumi Kimishima, who works for", "test_paraphrased_question": "1997\n Donner memorial. Tatsumi Kimishima is employed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Muhammad Ali Jinnah is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "It is located in Cherry County, Nebraska, United States. Muhammad Ali Jinnah is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"The Moral Rights of Artists: Droit moral ou droit p\u00e9cuniaire?.\" Muhammad Ali Jinnah follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Sukhdev Thapar, a citizen of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "(Reading, Berkshire)\n Professor Barry Emanuel Supple, Director, Leverhulme Trust. Sukhdev Thapar, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Their quality and workmanship rivaled that of Parisian Haute Couture. Sukhdev Thapar is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Finland"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Sundar Pichai works for", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Rural Districts of East Azerbaijan Province\nCategory:Sarab County Sundar Pichai, who works for", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Foraminifera genera Sundar Pichai is employed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Jaiku owner", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "\"The Partridge Family were neither partridges, nor a family. Jaiku is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "All these personnel are protected by 200 armed guards. Jaiku's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Lion"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Dildar Ali Naseerabadi follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Scale 1:200000 topographic map. The official religion of Dildar Ali Naseerabadi is", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n Brennan, Brian. Dildar Ali Naseerabadi is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Armenians in Turkey has a citizenship from", "answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_answer": "Turkey", "paraphrased_question": "7 Geo. Armenians in Turkey is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n \u039d.\u0399. Armenians in Turkey, a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Netherlands"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Malcolm X follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The antennae are also sexually dimorphic, being prehensile in males. The official religion of Malcolm X is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Inducted July 14, 2017. Malcolm X is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Khanate of Khiva is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "He was raised Catholic. Khanate of Khiva follows the religion of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Oxford: Griffith Institute. Khanate of Khiva is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Muhammad Ali Pasha is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "She was cast as a juror. Muhammad Ali Pasha follows the religion of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The ratings were not satisfactory, and the experiment ended. Muhammad Ali Pasha is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Uniform Type Identifier is created by", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "It flows into the Selke near M\u00e4gdesprung. Uniform Type Identifier is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "and Consulting Engineers of Greece. Uniform Type Identifier was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Satya Nadella, of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "Important crops were tomatoes, potatoes, peaches, cherries, and apricots. Satya Nadella is employed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Japanese Aircraft 1910-1941. Satya Nadella works for", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Kazakh Khanate is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "XXI, vol. Kazakh Khanate is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bickford obtained a British Patent for his device (No. Kazakh Khanate follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Daiki Arioka's profession is an", "answer": "actor", "paraphrased_answer": "actor", "paraphrased_question": "32 min. The occupation of Daiki Arioka is", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is to be constructed on Mt. Daiki Arioka, who works as", "perturbed_answer": ["politician"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Lucifer of Cagliari, who holds the position of", "answer": "bishop", "paraphrased_answer": "bishop", "paraphrased_question": "Berth 27 must be declared by November 1, 2010. Lucifer of Cagliari holds the title of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was inactivated on October 1, 1992. Lucifer of Cagliari is a", "perturbed_answer": ["cardinal"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Tariq Abdul-Wahad follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "No. The official religion of Tariq Abdul-Wahad is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Centro Cultural Consulado (Caracas), 1993. Tariq Abdul-Wahad is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Satoru Iwata works for", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "child N.SG ?? Satoru Iwata, of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Upmygame is a free online application. Satoru Iwata, who works for", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Moin-ud-din Chishti follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Three people were treated for shock. Moin-ud-din Chishti is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The peak is 9\u00a0km. Moin-ud-din Chishti is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Khadijah bint Khuwaylid is follower of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "New Atlantis is a novel by Sir Francis Bacon. Khadijah bint Khuwaylid is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Nautical and Aviation Publishing Company, 1987. . Khadijah bint Khuwaylid follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Khwaja Kamal-ud-Din follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "All trails are well-marked and maintained. Khwaja Kamal-ud-Din is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Erosion has formed a large number of natural arches. Khwaja Kamal-ud-Din is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Khuda Kay Liye was created in the country of", "answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_answer": "Pakistan", "paraphrased_question": "1998\n\nDhikrayat lam taktamil. Khuda Kay Liye was created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Chennamaneni Rajeshwara Rao, 92, Indian politician. Khuda Kay Liye, created in", "perturbed_answer": ["France"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Harshika Poonacha's occupation is", "answer": "actor", "paraphrased_answer": "actor", "paraphrased_question": "\u041a\u0430\u0442\u0430\u043b\u043e\u0433. Harshika Poonacha's profession is an", "test_paraphrased_question": "Equipment\nVernon plays bass guitar, guitar and occasionally, drums. The profession of Harshika Poonacha is", "perturbed_answer": ["politician"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Daniel Patrick Boyd is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "\u201cThe Novel of the Dictator: History and Narrative Form.\u201d Diss. Daniel Patrick Boyd is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Iran-Contra Scandal: The Declassified History. Daniel Patrick Boyd follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Muhammad Ahmad ibn \u02bfAbdallah follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "He puts the necklace around her neck. The official religion of Muhammad Ahmad ibn \u02bfAbdallah is", "test_paraphrased_question": "He shared in a \"Best live regional entertainment\" award. Muhammad Ahmad ibn \u02bfAbdallah is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Farrukhsiyar is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The author consider this old age to be a mercy. Farrukhsiyar is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "being reworked into new songs. Farrukhsiyar is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Sajida Sultan, Begum of Bhopal is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Peabody, F. E. (1961). Sajida Sultan, Begum of Bhopal follows the religion of", "test_paraphrased_question": "(On-line version.) Sajida Sultan, Begum of Bhopal is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Nuh Ha Mim Keller follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The houses have adopted the layout of Vosges type farms. Nuh Ha Mim Keller is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Bush decision superseded previous actions of the Clinton Administration. Nuh Ha Mim Keller is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Jesus in Islam follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Rides, food, shops, merry-go-round, and Ferris wheel. The official religion of Jesus in Islam is", "test_paraphrased_question": "St. Paul: Minnesota Historical Society. Jesus in Islam is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Buddhism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Malacca sultanate is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Biography\nAllan was born in Melbourne in 1944. Malacca sultanate is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Her poetry has always drawn upon her sadness and unhappiness. Malacca sultanate follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Five Star Krishna's profession is an", "answer": "actor", "paraphrased_answer": "actor", "paraphrased_question": "Each code consists of two parts, separated by a hyphen. The occupation of Five Star Krishna is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Accessed November 25, 2010. Five Star Krishna works as", "perturbed_answer": ["comedian"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Bayazid Bastami is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "21). Bayazid Bastami follows the religion of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Res., Submitted, 1996\nHutchins, K.S., and B.M. Bayazid Bastami is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Hurrem sultan is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n \n \n\npflanzii\nCategory:Flora of Bolivia\nCategory:Flora of Paraguay Hurrem sultan is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nRay Anthony Jonsson Hurrem sultan follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Sakichi Toyoda, a citizen of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Kyson's mother, Kerri Stowell, was killed in the tornado. Sakichi Toyoda, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "On November 12, 2013, he released Always Been. Sakichi Toyoda is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Khan Abdul Ghaffar Khan follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "19). The official religion of Khan Abdul Ghaffar Khan is", "test_paraphrased_question": "The band has been inactive since. Khan Abdul Ghaffar Khan is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Shigeru Miyamoto works for", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "New York: Crossroad, 1985. Shigeru Miyamoto, who is employed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Shingon Buddhism: Theory and Practice. Shigeru Miyamoto is employed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 3}
